Guide to the Israel Heritage Room Committee Collection, 1929-2013 UA.40.13
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Architectural Files, 1980-1986; VI.
  - Chetlin and Kaufman Designs, 1984-1986 (Map-case 30-2, Folder 4)
  - Pelzig Designs, 1983 (Map-case 30-2, Folder 5)
  - Kaufman Designs, 1983 (Map-case 30-2, Folder 6)